Students must do these things to improve their English.
學生必須做這些事情來提高他們的英語水平
Students placed in the Academic English Preparation (AEP) program
被安排在學術英語準備課程（AEP）中的學生
must work hard in class to learn and practice English.
必須在課堂上努力學習並且練習英語。
There are many things that students can do to ensure their English will improve quickly.
學生可以做很多事情來確保他們的英語能夠迅速提高。
English skills are divided into 4 categories:
英語技能分為四類：
Reading, writing, speaking, and listening.
讀，寫，說，聽。
To improve their rating skills,
為了提高他們的評分技巧
Students should read for pleasure everyday.
學生應該養成每天閱讀的習慣。
If they read 45-60 minutes
如果他們閱讀45-60分鐘
their comprehension and vocabulary knowledge will improve
他們的閱讀理解能力和詞彙量將會提高很多
Students should ask themselves questions about the stories or texts they are reading
學生應該問自己關於他們正在閱讀的故事或文章的問題
The "who, what where when and why" questions are best.
閱讀的故事中，”有誰? 發生了什麼? 在哪裡發生? 什麼時候發生? 發生的原因?”，這些都是學生可以問自己的問題
For all comprehension assignments
對於所有的有關閱讀理解能力的作業
Students should make sure they change all incorrect answers.
學生應確保他們更改所有不正確的答案
When reading a novel, short story or fiction text,
在閱讀小說，短篇小說或小說文本的時侯
students should try to visualize the story in their minds.
學生應該嘗試在腦海中想像這個故事
To improve writing skills,
為了提高寫作技巧
students should keep a log or journal of new words.
學生應該保持自己有一本記錄新詞彙的日誌
It is important to fully understand the topic and purpose
在做任何寫作作業之前，
before doing any writing assignment.
充分理解主題和這篇文章的目的是非常重要的
Planning a writing assignment is very important.
對寫作作業而言，在寫作之前的規劃是很重要的
Editing work after finishing a first draft is essential.
完成初稿後編輯修改也是至關重要的
Students should pay attention to all grammar and vocabulary lessons
學生應該注意所有的語法和詞彙的用法
and try to use the grammar and vocabulary learned
並且嘗試使用新學的語法和詞彙在他們所寫的作業中
To further improve their writing skills,
為了進一步提高寫作技巧，
students should write letters,
學生應該寫信，
write in a diary, write descriptive emails,
寫日記，撰寫描述性電子郵件，
and write in a reading log
並寫閱讀日誌
and should do so in complete sentences as much as possible.
而且盡可能用完整的句子。
To improve their speaking,
為了改善他們的口語溝通
students should ask questions often in class
學生應該經常在課堂上提問
and participate in English conversations.
並參與課上的英語會話
Outside of school,
在學校外面
students should make an effort to speak English whenever possible.
學生應該盡可能講英語。
It helps if students have friends from another country.
如果學生有來自其他國家的朋友，這也可以幫助學生提高英語口語能力
When students have a oral class presentation to do,
當學生需要在課上做口語演講時，
They should practice beforehand until they feel confident,
他們應該事先練習，直到他們感到自信
working on pronunciation, intonation, and stress will help students speak with more clarity,
他們應該花時間糾正發音，語調和壓力。這樣也可以幫助學生更清晰地用英文表述，
To improve their listening,
為了改善他們的英語聽力
students should listen actively; this will help with understanding.
學生應該積極傾聽，這將有助於理解。
While participating in conversations,
在參與對話時
a good listener can help acquire a deeper understanding of the subject.
一個好的傾聽者可以幫助更深入地了解所談的話題。
Students can learn a lot by listening to English news reports,
學生可以通過聽英文新聞報導、
News reports in English, TV shows, and TED talks.
電視節目和TED談話，可以學到很多東西，
In class, while the teacher talks about a topic,
在課堂上，當老師談論一個話題時
the students should listen and take notes.
學生應該傾聽並做筆記。
This is active listening
這是積極主動的傾聽
Progressing in English takes time and effort,
提高英語能力需要時間和精力，
and if students can use English for many hours a day during class and after class,
如果學生在上課和下課後每天都可以使用英語數小時的話，
their ability to communicate fluently
他們使用英文來流利溝通的能力將以良好的、強勁的步伐發展。